—— SEBASTIAN CAMPOS ——

CONTACT

- +51 955331665
- Sebasadolfo123@gmail.com
- Sebastian-campos.com

PROFILE

Web programmer with 1 year of experience, I am someone proactive with a great attraction for challenges, I have a great passion for technology and that is the reason why I always try to be updated and I have been self-taught studying new things with which to improve my performance.

I have knowledge in:

HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | Jquery | Javascript | React Python | Flask | PHP | MySql

APTITUDES

- ADAPTABILITY
- Concentration
- VERSATILITY
- CREATIVE PROBLEM SOLVING
- ANALYSIS CAPACITY
- Active listening
- ° TIME MANAGEMENT
- TEAMWORK
- Effective communication

EXPERIENCE

Vicios Burger

11/2021 - 12/2021

As a freelancer, my first job was to create a landing page for a fast food restaurant near my area, where the products they offer, the stores they had and a contact form were shown; use HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, JAVASCRIPT and take care of everything related to the creation of the page; Currently the page is no longer online because an e-commerce is planned.

Samishop

04/2022 - actual

At samishop I work as a front-end developer, in charge of the layout, design, improvement of functionalities, data capture and data delivery; I have worked on various projects, the vast majority of e-commerce using HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY AND REACT.

EDUCATION

Icpna

01/2018 - 03/2021

English language learning from basic to advanced.

Isil

03/2019 - 06/2022

I studied Software Engineering at the Isil institute, where I learned about fundamentals and basic programming things.

Udemy

2021 - 2022

Throughout 2021 and 2022 I have taken different courses on the Udemy platform to complement and improve my knowledge.